<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
	Why XML and not JSON? Simple. JSON is an Object Notation. It's not very
	good for expressing information in a format like this due to it being
	designed to describe programming constructs, rather than informational
	constructs. XML on the other hand is perfect for this, which is probably
	why HTML was based on it.
	
	There are two types of tags; "entry" and "ignore". The encyclopedia system
	will stop looking when it encounters an ignore. So, if you put an ignore
	with a specific damage value before an entry that matches all items of that
	type, the ignore will be preferred and the item will have no encyclopedia
	entry. However, when there are two entries, one with a more specific
	definition, the later one is appended onto the earlier one. To prevent
	this, the more specific one can be put before the general one and then an
	ignore tag for the more specific def can be put after the specific entry.
	for example:
		<entry def="farrago:potato@5">Potato:5</entry>
		<entry def="farrago:potato">Potato</entry>
		results in 'Potato:5 Potato'
	and:
		<entry def="farrago:potato@5">Potato:5</entry>
		<ignore def="farrago:potato@5"/>
		<entry def="farrago:potato">Potato</entry>
		results in 'Potato:5'
	
	All tags must have a 'def' field. A def must start with a fully qualified
	block or item name; e.g. 'minecraft:stone', 'farrago:rifle'. An @ sign is
	a separator between the item's name and it's required damage value. If
	the damage value is omitted, all damage values are accepted. A value of
	32767 also acts as a wildcard.
	Finally, a Mojangson NBT definition can be enclosed in curly braces at the
	end to require certain NBT tags to be present. As with damage values, if
	omitted, any values are accepted. If trailed by a '?', then any extra tags
	on the item are ignored. So, {Foo:Bar} matches {Foo:Bar} but not
	{Foo:Bar,Baz:Quux}, but {Foo:Bar}? will match both.
	
	('Mojangson' here means the format used by command blocks.)
 -->
<!--              this file is formatted to fit in 80 columns               -->
<encyclopedia>
	<entry def="farrago:kahur">
		A strange weapon that uses everyday items as ammunition.
		The more complex they are, the more damage they do.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:kahur{KahurPumpMaterial:GLASS}?">
		This one is particular has been outfitted to only fire potions.
		These potions will break when hitting something and will apply their
		effect to nearby mobs.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:kahur{KahurPumpMaterial:POTATO}?">
		This one is particular has been outfitted to  only fire potatoes.
		Why would you make a gun that can only shoot potatoes?
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:kahur{KahurPumpMaterial:GLOW}?">
		This one is particular has been outfitted to only fire torches.
		These torches will stick onto any walls they hit.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:kahur{KahurPumpMaterial:OBSIDIAN}?">
		This one is particular has been outfitted to only attempt to fire
		gunpowder. This results in it violently backfiring whenever it is shot.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:kahur{KahurPumpMaterial:ENDER}?">
		This one is particular has been outfitted to fire items in a
		predictable order.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:kahur{KahurPumpMaterial:PLATINUM}?">
		This one is particular has been outfitted to fire items in a
		predictable order.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:kahur{KahurPumpMaterial:IRIDIUM}?">
		This one is particular has been outfitted to fire items in a
		predictable order.
	</entry>
	
	<ignore def="farrago:rubble@5"/>
	
	<entry def="farrago:rubble">
		Leftover trash from scrapping an object. Can be used as fuel in a
		furnace, but it will only last until all flammable material is burnt.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:vividOrb">
		This orb is capable of storing the very essence of a color.
		The art of making these in bright colors has been lost, and as such
		those can now only be found in abandoned ruins.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:combustor">
		This machine uses gunpowder or TNT as an alternative, and very fast,
		way to smelt items. Every smelting operation has a small chance to
		smelt two at once, and an even smaller chance to smelt three.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:scrapper">
		This machine can break down items and blocks into their component
		parts. Sound high tech? It's not. Given any furnace fuels, this
		machine will repeatedly smash a block or item until it's components
		are nothing but dust. Only gems and metals can be recovered this way;
		everything else is lost and converted to rubble. This is, however, a
		very effective way of converting gems and ingots directly into dusts
		with no loss.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:resource@0">
		A solid block of Nether Stars. You're either rich, insane, or both.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:blunderbuss">
		This somewhat shoddy gun uses gunpowder to detonate pieces of gravel
		into tiny shards, perfect for tearing up your enemies. It is highly
		inaccurate, and is effectively useless at range.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:blunderbuss{Zealon:1b}?">
		This one in particular has been outfitted with a strange upgrade
		made from stranger materials; the effect appears to be that the fire
		rate is unlimited.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:rifle">
		This state-of-the-art rifle can use cells filled with varying types
		of dusts and powders to cause reactions of both chemical and magical
		nature, and then harnesses them to shoot beams with different effects.
		Sneak while firing to change modes. Be careful not to overcharge it!
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:dust">
		Don't breathe this.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:dust@8">
		This dust is somewhat unstable, but emeralds are known to act as a good
		catalyst to stabilize it for use.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:ingot@0">
		A solid bar of Yttrium. Yttrium has a variety of uses, including the
		manufacture of ray guns, reacting with glowstone to make an eternal
		light, and being alloyed with copper to make a highly conductive
		metal.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:ingot@1">
		A solid bar of Yttric Copper. Yttric Copper is an alloy of Yttrium and
		copper, and it is highly conductive. It is also useful for reinforcing
		things, as it is less brittle than pure Yttrium.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:cell@0">
		An empty cell, made from Yttrium and Yttric Copper. Maybe you should
		fill it with something?
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:cell@1">
		This cell has been filled with Redstone and Copper, which when fired
		out of a Yttric Rifle, cause a powerful corrosive reaction.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:cell@2">
		This cell has been filled with Glowstone and Yttrium, which react
		together making an eternal light.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:cell@3">
		This cell has been filled with gold and diamond (but mostly gold, you
		cheapskate), which when fired out of a Yttric Rifle, are capable of
		breaking almost any block.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:cell@4">
		This cell has been filled with iron and gunpowder, which make
		explosions. Are you surprised? I'm surprised.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:cell@5">
		This cell has been filled with emerald dust and Ender Pearl dust,
		which allows the Yttric Rifle to act as a teleporter. The innate magic
		left in the Ender Pearl pulls the beam toward the ground, where
		strongholds are located.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:cell@6">
		This cell has been filled with Redstone, Copper, and Blaze Powder. It's
		the same as a Redstone-Copper cell, but with the added ability to set
		things on fire.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:caquelon">
		An empty iron container for a variety of foods.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:fondue@0">
		A caquelon filled with a delicious mixture of molten cheeses. How it
		stays hot is anyone's guess.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:fondue@1">
		A caquelon filled with a variety of meats and a bit of bread. Very
		filling.
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:fondue@2">
		A caquelon filled with melted chocolate. Anyone have a strawberry?
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:fondue@3">
		A caquelon filled with apple cider... wait, why'd you fill a caquelon
		with cider? Isn't that what bottles are for?
	</entry>
	<entry def="farrago:fondue@4">
		&#x00A7;kSaiba sanda saida, saiba sanda saida
	</entry>
</encyclopedia>